export const stuff = [
  {
    id: "6244374b746187c5e7be9344",
    correctAnswer:
      "It is used as a solvent for lacquer, floor polishes and resins.",
    choices: [
      "It is used for surface purification, bleaching, odour removal and water disinfection.",
      "It is used in manufacture of pulp and paper, alumina, soap and detergents.",
      "It is used as a solvent for lacquer, floor polishes and resins.",
      "It is used as oscillators in radios, watches.",
    ],
    question: "What is the chemical trichloromethane often used for?",
  },
  {
    id: "62433403cfaae40c12961419",
    category: "science",
    question: "What would you call a baby frog?",
    correctAnswer: "A Tadpole",
    choices: ["A Piglet", "A Calf", "A Tadpole", "A Maggot"],
  },
  {
    id: "6243333fcfaae40c129613cd",
    category: "science",
    question: "What is the word for a young bird?",
    correctAnswer: "A Chick",
    choices: ["An Owlet", "A Bunny", "A Chick", "A Poult"],
  },
  {
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504b6",
    category: "science",
    question: "What is Phytology the study of?",
    correctAnswer: "plants; botany",
    choices: [
      "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study",
      "the study or exploration of caves",
      "wonders, or monsters",
      "plants; botany",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504cb",
    category: "science",
    question: "What is Paleoclimatology the study of?",
    correctAnswer: "prehistoric climates",
    choices: [
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life",
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being",
      "prehistoric climates",
      "cancer",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "6243357dcfaae40c129614ad",
    category: "science",
    question: "What is the word for a young turtle?",
    correctAnswer: "A Hatchling",
    choices: ["A Piglet", "A Maggot", "A Hatchling", "A Lamb"],
  },
  {
    id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504cb",
    category: "science",
    question: "What is Paleoclimatology the study of?",
    correctAnswer: "prehistoric climates",
    choices: [
      "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life",
      "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being",
      "prehistoric climates",
      "cancer",
    ],
  },
];

// export const stuff = [
//   {
//     id: "6243333fcfaae40c129613cd",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What is the word for a young bird?",
//     correctAnswer: "A Chick",
//     choices: ["An Owlet", "A Bunny", "A Chick", "A Poult"],
//   },
//   {
//     id: "6243333fcfaae40c129613cd",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What is the word for a young bird?",
//     correctAnswer: "A Chick",
//     choices: ["An Owlet", "A Bunny", "A Chick", "A Poult"],
//   },
//   {
//     id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504b6",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What is Phytology the study of?",
//     correctAnswer: "plants; botany",
//     choices: [
//       "the science of preparing and handling microscopic objects for study",
//       "the study or exploration of caves",
//       "wonders, or monsters",
//       "plants; botany",
//     ],
//   },
//   {
//     id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504cb",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What is Paleoclimatology the study of?",
//     correctAnswer: "prehistoric climates",
//     choices: [
//       "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life",
//       "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being",
//       "prehistoric climates",
//       "cancer",
//     ],
//   },
//   {
//     id: "62433403cfaae40c12961419",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What would you call a baby frog?",
//     correctAnswer: "A Tadpole",
//     choices: ["A Piglet", "A Calf", "A Tadpole", "A Maggot"],
//   },
//   {
//     id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504cb",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What is Paleoclimatology the study of?",
//     correctAnswer: "prehistoric climates",
//     choices: [
//       "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life",
//       "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being",
//       "prehistoric climates",
//       "cancer",
//     ],
//   },
//   {
//     id: "6243357dcfaae40c129614ad",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What is the word for a young turtle?",
//     correctAnswer: "A Hatchling",
//     choices: ["A Piglet", "A Maggot", "A Hatchling", "A Lamb"],
//   },
//   {
//     id: "622a1c377cc59eab6f9504cb",
//     category: "science",
//     question: "What is Paleoclimatology the study of?",
//     correctAnswer: "prehistoric climates",
//     choices: [
//       "a branch of soil science that studies the influence of soil on life",
//       "the study and science of phenomena as distinct from the science of actual existence or being",
//       "prehistoric climates",
//       "cancer",
//     ],
//   },
// ];
